JULIUS OGUNNIYI

22, Bolarin Street, Off Pab Bustop, Ikotun-Egbe, Lagos, Nigeria. +2349024420929

ogunniyi.julius12@gmail.com · https://ng.linkedin.com/in/julius-ogunniyi-97884b199 ·

https://portfolio-chi-wheat-67.vercel.app/port.html

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Newly graduated self-motivated Web Developer with comprehensive experience of 2 years of developing websites. Passionate and hardworking to deliver dynamic interfaces and clean code on deadlines, strong in HTML, CSS and JavaScript programmer and also WordPress template creation.

EXPERIENCE

Makintouch Consulting - System Administrator/Junior Web Developer March 2020 - October 2020.

- Configured, tested and maintained network equipment.
- Planned and implemented upgrades to system hardware and software.
- Resolved issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service.
- Worked with users to determine areas in need of improvement.
- Implemented, maintained, developed and tested the installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments.
- I was also working with the senior full stack developer and learning web design.
- Worked on the organization website with wordpress, developed some basic websites using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Freelance - Front End Developer June 2021 – January 2022.

- Converted User Interface designs into functional web applications
- Worked with a team of Mobile App Engineers and Back End Engineer to achieve a project.
- Worked with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Jquery.

Makintouch Consulting – Front End Developer Feb 2022 – Present.

- Created custom websites by harnessing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript skills.
- Improved website navigation with clear and intuitive UX mapping.

- Integrated Flutterwave third party platform API with a website.
- Designed web pages to enhance branding and navigation.
- Designed graphics with Adobe Creative Cloud to achieve brand goals.
- Boosted website performance and stability through planned maintenance and targeted troubleshooting.

CERTIFICATES OF TRAINING

- Web Development HIIT PLC (July August, 2019).
- CompTIA A+ (September, 2020).
- AWS

EDUCATION

Academic Qualifications

- **Bowen University, Iwo, Osun state** B.Sc. In Computer Science and Information Technology (**September, 2017 November 2021**).
- Lagos State Senior Model College, Badore, Ajah, Lagos West Africa Senior School Certificate Examination (June 2017).

SKILLS

- Website optimisation
- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Graphics Design
- HTML coding
- WordPress
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Jquery
- UI/UX design
- Web development projects
- GitHub

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

• English, Yoruba.

INTERESTS

- Coding
- Music
- Video games

REFERENCES

• Available on request.